// Joel Herrero Full Stack Developer

☐ (+34) 650 723 783 | ⋈ joelv2@gmail.com ☑ elniu.dev | ♠ based on Barcelona | ♀ letjoel



Profile

Since I was 15 years old I have been passionate about creating websites and applications. Despite this precocious passion I had the need to better understand the world around me in a humanistic sense. I had the opportunity to gain a solid professional background and a growth mindset, whose guided me to prioritize honest and transparent communication. I am always hungry for knowledge and I always try to solve situations with flexibility, empathy and firmness. I really enjoy when programming, because I love making the imaginary come true.

Education

Bootcamp

FACTORÍA F5

Full stack developer roadmap (850h).

Bachelor's degree in Humanities

UPF (Pompeu Fabra University)

Mention in philosophy.

First level degree in Psychology

UNEL

IT skills

✓ Javascript, Typescript.

✓ NodeJs, NestJs, Express, Socket.io.

✓ MongoDB, MySQL, PostgreSQL.

✓ React, Redux, TailwindCSS, SASS.

√ TDD, Jest, Supertest.

✓ Git, AGILE, Clean code.

Languages

English C1 (British Council).

Spanish. Catalan.

Projects

Elected

GAME DEVELOPER

Game programming using C# and Unity. Game design (UI, economy balancing, game loop).

Barcelona, Spain

Barcelona, Spain

Barcelona, Spain

Barcelona, Spain Sep. 2004 – Jun. 2006

Sep. 2008 - Jun. 2014

Oct. 2022 - Apr. 2023

Sep. 2021 – Oct. 2022

Hotel PMR

WEB DEVELOPER

Web site design and implementation for an hotel with a fully integrated booking system connected to main OTAs (Wordpress).

Barcelona, Spain Sep. 2018 - Jan. 2019

Barcelona, Spain

May 2014 - Sept. 2014

Daily report tool

SOFTWARE DEVELOPED

Full programming and deployment of a software aimed to register diary activity in a PSAP center.

Barcelona, Spain Jan. 2009 – Jun. 2009

OsCommerce based full development of an e-commerce (PHP based).

Hearts of Iron MOD

Local business store
WEB DEVELOPER

GAME MODDING & WEB DEV

Complete mod of a popular strategy game (custom sprites, AI improved, event triggers, UI). Development of a gamers website (large community).

Barcelona, Spain

Jul. 2004 – Dec. 2004

Experience

Emergency coordinator center PSAP

OPERATIONS TECHNICIAN

Supervisory of emergencies in progress. Protocol design. Quality monitoring. Formations. GIS.

Barcelona, Spain

Oct. 2010 - Sep. 2014 & Jul. 2019 - 2023

CVital

DAILY MANAGER

HR management and marketing.

Barcelona, Spain

Jan. 2019 – Jul. 2019

Ahora

MANAGER

Málaga, Spain

Sep. 2014 – Sep. 2018

HR management, finances, marketing and web site management of a countryside hotel.

Emergency coordinator center PSAP

COORDINATOR

HR management in high stressing situations (emergencies). Selective training for new employees and retraining.

Barcelona, Spain

Jan. 2009 - Oct. 2010